export const questions = [
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What does the 'M' in MERN stack stand for?",
    "options": ["MongoDB", "MySQL", "MariaDB", "Machine Learning"],
    "answer": "MongoDB"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "Which library is used in the MERN stack for building user interfaces?",
    "options": ["Angular", "Vue", "React", "jQuery"],
    "answer": "React"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Which part of MERN is used as the backend server framework?",
    "options": ["MongoDB", "React", "Express", "Node.js"],
    "answer": "Express"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Node.js runs on which environment?",
    "options": ["Web Browser", "Runtime Environment", "Mobile App", "Database Server"],
    "answer": "Runtime Environment"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Which database does MERN stack use?",
    "options": ["PostgreSQL", "MongoDB", "Firebase", "Oracle"],
    "answer": "MongoDB"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Express is mainly used for?",
    "options": ["Designing UI", "Managing Database", "Handling HTTP Requests", "Styling Websites"],
    "answer": "Handling HTTP Requests"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "React components must return how many root elements?",
    "options": ["Multiple", "Only One", "Zero", "At Least Two"],
    "answer": "Only One"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Which method is used to create a MongoDB database?",
    "options": ["createDB()", "use <db_name>", "initDB()", "new Database()"],
    "answer": "use <db_name>"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Which command starts a Node.js application?",
    "options": ["npm start", "node app.js", "run app", "serve app"],
    "answer": "node app.js"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Which hook is commonly used for state management in React?",
    "options": ["useFetch", "useData", "useState", "useAPI"],
    "answer": "useState"
  }
]

